A Guide to the Records of T. Marshall Hahn Jr, 1962-1974
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series III, 1967-1969
  - C-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1074)
  - Centennial, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1075)
  - War Memorial Chapel, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1076)
  - Chemistry: Dr. Alan F. Clifford, head, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1077)
  - Chemical Engineering: Dr. N.F. Murphy, Acting head, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1078)
  - College Calendar, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1079)
  - Commandant of Cadets, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1080)
  - Civil Rights, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1081)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1082)
  - Faculty Review Board, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1083)
  - VPI Facilities, Inc. Committee, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1084)
  - Committees: Art Objects, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1085)
  - Building Committee, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1086)
  - Catalog Committee, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1087)
  - Commencement Committee, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1088)
  - Computer Committee, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1089)
  - Committees: Employee Benefits, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1090)
  - Committees: Disciplinary, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1091)
  - Committees: Fraternity and Sorority, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1092)
  - Faculty Senate Steering Committee, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1093)
  - Graduate Committee, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1094)
  - Committee: Graduate Dormitory, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1095)
  - Judicial Committee, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1096)
  - Library Committee, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1097)
  - Committees: Military Affairs, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1098)
  - Miscellaneous Committee, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1099)
  - Committee: Orientation, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1100)
  - Social and Cultural Committee, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1101)
  - Committees: Scheduling and Registration, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1102)
  - Traffic Committee, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1103)
  - Traffic Appeals Subcommittee, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1104)
  - Student Budget Board Committee, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1105)
  - Committees: Student Forums, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 1106)
  - Student Activities Committee #1, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1107)
  - Student Activities Committee #2, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1108)
  - Community Colleges: Dr. Dana Hamel, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1109)
  - Community Concert, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1110)
  - Computing Center, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1111)
  - Conferences, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1112)
  - Consulting 1, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1113)
  - Consulting 2, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1114)
  - Cooperative Education National Commission, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1115)
  - Cooperative Program, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1116)
  - Council of Presidents, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1117)
  - Counseling Center: Dr. Thomas E. Cook, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1118)
  - D-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1119)
  - Dairy Science: Dr. J.R. Nichols, Head, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1120)
  - The Danforth Foundation, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1121)
  - Deans: General, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1122)
  - Dedication: Donaldson Brown Center for Continuing Education, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1123)
  - Dedications, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1124)
  - Development, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1125)
  - Development: Mr. W.B. Bell, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1126)
  - Dining Hall: Mr. H.P. King, Director, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1127)
  - E-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1128)
  - Economics: Dr. W.E. Schmidt, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1129)
  - Editorial Projects for Education, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1130)
  - Education: Dr. Rufus Beamer, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1131)
  - Electrical Engineering: Dr. W.A. Blackwell, Head, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1132)
  - Engineering and Building: Governor's Office, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1133)
  - Engineering, College of: Dean Willis G. Worchester, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1134)
  - Engineering Mechanics: Prof. Dan H. Pletta, Head, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1135)
  - English: Dr. Wilson Snipes, Head, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1136)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1137)
  - Entomology Department: Dr. J.M. Grayson, Head, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1138)
  - Executive Bulletins, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1139)
  - Extension-Continuing Education Center: Dr. Roger L. Smith, Director, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1140)
  - Extension: General, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1141)
  - Extension Division: Dr. W.E. Skelton, Dean, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1142)
  - Extension: State Technical Services- Dr. Roger L. Smith, Director, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1143)
  - F-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1144)
  - Faculty Lists, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1145)
  - Ferrum Junior College, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1146)
  - First National Exchange Bank of Virginia, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1147)
  - Football, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1148)
  - Foreign Service Institute, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1149)
  - Foreign Languages: Dr. J. Bruhn, Head, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1150)
  - G-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1151)
  - Forestry and Wildlife: Dr. J.F. Hasner, Head, 1968 (Box 30, Folder 1152)
  - Gallagher Presidents Report, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1153)
  - Geological Science: Dr. B.N. Cooper, Head, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1154)
  - Glee Club: Mr. Stanley Kingma, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1155)
  - Governor of Virginia: The Honorable Mills E. Godwin, Jr., 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1156)
  - Governor's Day, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1157)
  - Graduate School: Dean F.W. Bull, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1158)
  - H-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1159)
  - Dr. Hahn- Governorship, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1160)
  - Dr. T. Marshall Hahn, Jr.: Personal, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1161)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1162)
  - Higher Education Facilities Act, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1163)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1164)
  - History: Dr. Robert G. Landen, Head, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1165)
  - Honor Court, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1166)
  - Homecoming, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1167)
  - Home Economics, College of: Dean Laura Jane Harper, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1168)
  - Horticulture Department: Dr. Howard A. Rollins, Jr., Head, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1169)
  - Hospital, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1170)
  - Housing, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1171)
  - I-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1172)
  - Industrial Development, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1173)
  - Industrial Engineering: Dr. Paul E. Torgersen, Head, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1174)
  - Infirmary: Dr. E.R. Irwin, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1175)
  - Information Services #1: Mr. W.H. Strother, Director, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1176)
  - Information Services #2: Mr. W.H. Strother, Director, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1177)
  - Institutional Research, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1178)
  - Invitations, Miscellaneous #1: January thru March, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1179)
  - Invitations, Miscellaneous #2: April thru June, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1180)
  - Invitations, Miscellaneous #3: July thru December, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1181)
  - Invitations, Inauguration, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1182)
  - J-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1183)
  - Johnston, J. Ambler, 1968 (Box 31, Folder 1184)
  - K-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1185)
  - L-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1186)
  - The Lane Company, Inc., Board of Visitors, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1187)
  - Legislation, General #1, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1188)
  - Legislation, General #2, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1189)
  - Library: Mr. F.C. Shirk, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1190)
  - M- miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1191)
  - Mathematics: Dr. Leon W. Rutland, Head, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1192)
  - MASC, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1193)
  - Mechanical Engineering: Dr. J. Beverly Jones, Head, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1194)
  - Military, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1195)
  - N-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1196)
  - NASA, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1197)
  - National Research Council, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1198)
  - Naming Buildings, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1199)
  - National Science Foundation, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1200)
  - NCAA, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1201)
  - National Defense Education Act (NDEA) Fellowship, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1202)
  - O-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1203)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1204)
  - Oak Ridge Associated Universities, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1205)
  - Organization, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1206)
  - Peace Corps, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1207)
  - Personnel, Mr. Albin T. Butt, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1208)
  - Personnel- Richmond: Mr. J.W. Garber, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1209)
  - Physical Education: Dr. W.E. McCubbin, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1210)
  - Philippines, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1211)
  - Philosophy and Religion: Dr. Norman L. Grover, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1212)
  - Physical Plant Planning #1: Mr. H.P.C. Vandenburg, Director, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1213)
  - Physical Plant Planning #2: Mr. H.P.C. Vandenburg, Director, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1214)
  - Physics: Dr. J.A. Jacobs, Head, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1215)
  - Placement: Dr. W.H. Cato, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1216)
  - Planning: Division of Governor's Office, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1217)
  - Political Science: Dr. Joseph L. Bernd, Head, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1218)
  - Poly-Scientific, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1219)
  - Poultry Science: Dr. C.E. Howes, Head, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1220)
  - Purchasing: Mr. James L. Shotts, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1221)
  - Q-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1222)
  - R-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1223)
  - Registrar: Mr. R.E. Keller, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1224)
  - Regional Education Laboratory, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1225)
  - Regional Education Laboratory (REL) #2, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1226)
  - Research Corporation, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1227)
  - Research Division: Dean W.B. Harrison, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1228)
  - Reston, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1229)
  - Retirement- Faculty, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1230)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1230a)
  - S-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1231)
  - Sabbatical Leaves, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1232)
  - Savage, Mr. Lon K., 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1233)
  - Salaries, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1234)
  - Scholarships: Harry F. Bird, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1235)
  - Scholarships and Grants # 1, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1236)
  - Scholarships and Grants #2, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1237)
  - Scholarships and Grants #3, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1238)
  - Sociology, Department of: Dr. Leland B. Tate, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1239)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1240)
  - Smithfield, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1241)
  - Security Office: Mr. I.E. Nickols, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1242)
  - Speech Material, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1243)
  - Speaking Engagements: Correspondence #1, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1244)
  - Speaking Engagements: Correspondence #2, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1245)
  - Speaking Engagements: Correspondence #3, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1246)
  - Philip Sporn: Correspondence and Fund, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1247)
  - State Board of Education, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1248)
  - State Council of Higher Education, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1249)
  - Statistics: Dr. Boyd Harshburger, Head, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1250)
  - Status of Women, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1251)
  - Student Activities Fee, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1252)
  - Student Housing: Mr. Hardey, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1253)
  - Student Affairs: Dean of Students, Dr. J.W. Dean #1, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1254)
  - Student Affairs: Dean of Students, Dr. J.W. Dean #2, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1255)
  - Student Affairs: Dean of Students, Dr. J.W. Dean #3, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1255)
  - Student Affairs: Dean of Students, Dr. J.W. Dean #3, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1256)
  - Student Letters: Others, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1257)
  - Student Affairs: Dean of Women, Dean Martha Harder, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1258)
  - Student Affairs: Dean Al Payne, 1968 (Box 33, Folder 1259)
  - Student Affairs: Dean of Men, J. Gordon Brown, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1260)
  - Student Letters: To and From, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1261)
  - Student Organizations, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1262)
  - Student Government Association #1, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1263)
  - Student Government Association #2, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1264)
  - Student Union, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1265)
  - T-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1266)
  - Tech Festival, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1267)
  - Thesis Proposal, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1268)
  - Treasurer: Mr. James F. Boone, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1269)
  - TIAA, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1270)
  - TRW, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1271)
  - University Council #1, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1272)
  - University Council #2, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1273)
  - University Council #3, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1274)
  - University Council #4, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1275)
  - University Council (June) #1, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1276)
  - University Council (June) #2, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1277)
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1278)
  - TUMS, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1279)
  - University Council #5, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1280)
  - University Council #6, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1281)
  - University Research Park, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1282)
  - V-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1283)
  - VARC, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1284)
  - Veterinary Science: Dr. Douglas F. Watson, Head, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 1285)
  - Vice President for Academic Affairs: Dr. W.W. Brandt, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1286)
  - Vice President for Administration: Mr. S.K. Cassell, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1287)
  - Vice President for Administration: Presidents Funds, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1288)
  - Virginia State Highway, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1289)
  - Virginia Agricultural Conference Board, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1290)
  - Virginia Department of Agriculture, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1291)
  - Virginia State College, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1292)
  - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1293)
  - Virginia Tech Athletic Association, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1294)
  - VPI Educational Foundation, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1295)
  - Virginia Tech Student Aid, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 1296)
  - Virginia Truck Experiment Station, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1297)
  - Visiting Scholar Program, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1298)
  - W-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1299)
  - Water Resources, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1300)
  - Wine Awards, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1301)
  - YMCA, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1302)
  - Alumni Alphabetical #1, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1303)
  - Alumni: Alphabetical #2, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1304)
  - Alumni Association: General #1, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1305)
  - Alumni Association: General #2, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1306)
  - Alumni Contributions: Alphabetical, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1307)
  - American Association for Higher Education, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1308)
  - American Association for University Professors, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1309)
  - American Council on Education, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1310)
  - Animal Science: Prof. George W. Litton, Head, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1311)
  - Animal Industry Day, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1312)
  - Appalachian Institute, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1313)
  - Applications: Positions, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1314)
  - Architecture, College of: Charles Burchard, Dean, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1315)
  - A-miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1316)
  - Accounting: Dr. R.J. Patten, Head, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1317)
  - Accountant: Mr. Carl E. Burke, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1318)
  - Accrediting: National Commission of Accrediting-ECPD, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1319)
  - American Association of University Women, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1320)
  - Admissions and Records #1: Dr. M.P. Lacy, Head, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1321)
  - Admissions and Records #2: Dr. M.P. Lacy, Head, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1322)
  - Agriculture, College of: Dr. James E. Martin, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1323)
- Series IV, 1969-1970
  - Agricultural Economics, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1324)
  - Agricultural Engineering: U.F. Earp, Acting Head, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1325)
  - Agriculture: Resident Instruct, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1326)
  - Agronomy: Dr. T.B. Hutcheson, Head, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1327)
  - Air University, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1328)
  - Aircraft, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1329)
  - Alcoholic Beverage Control Board, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1330)
  - Airport, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1331)
  - Alumni Association President, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1332)
  - Arts and Sciences, College of, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1333)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1334)
  - Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities-Southern, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1335)
  - Association of State Colleges and Universities, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1336)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1337)
  - Association of State Universities and Land Grant Colleges- National, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1338)
  - Attorney General of Virginia, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1339)
  - Auxiliary Enterprises and University Services: Mr. Swink, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1340)
  - B-miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1341)
  - Bailey Research Trust, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1342)
  - Basketball, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1343)
  - Bequests, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1344)
  - Biochemistry and Nutrition: Dr. R.R. Schmidt, Acting Head, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1345)
  - Biographies, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1346)
  - Biology: Dr. R.A. Peterson, Head, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1347)
  - Buildings and Grounds: Dr. W.M. Sterret, Director, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1348)
  - Board of Visitors: Correspondence with Members, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1349)
  - Blacksburg, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1350)
  - Boards of Visitors #1, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1351)
  - Boards of Visitors #2, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1352)
  - Budget Division: Mr. L.M. Kuhn, Director, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1353)
  - Budget Matters #1, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1354)
  - Budget Matters #2, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1355)
  - Business, College of: Dr. H.H. Mitchell, Dean, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1356)
  - Business Manager: Mr. E.B. Evans, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1357)
  - Campus Governance Program, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1358)
  - C-miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1359)
  - Building Committee, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1360)
  - Catalog Committee, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1361)
  - Centennial, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1362)
  - Chemistry: Dr. Alan F. Clifford, Head, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1363)
  - Civil Engineering: Dr. H.M. Marris, Head, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1364)
  - Civil Rights, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1365)
  - College Calendar, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1366)
  - Commandant of Cadets, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1367)
  - Commencement Committee, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1368)
  - Commencement Exercises, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1369)
  - Commission on Faculty Affairs, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1370)
  - Commission on Research and Graduate Studies, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1371)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Student Affairs, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1372)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Studies, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1373)
  - Computer Committee, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1374)
  - Committees: Employee Benefits, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1375)
  - Committees: Fraternities and Sororities, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1376)
  - Committees: Graduate Dormitory, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1377)
  - Graduate Committee, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1378)
  - Judicial Committee, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1379)
  - Library Committee, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1380)
  - Committees: Military Affairs, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1381)
  - Committees: Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1382)
  - Committees: Orientation, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1383)
  - Committees: Scheduling and Registration, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1384)
  - Committees: Scholarship and Student Aid, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1385)
  - Student Activities Committee, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1386)
  - Traffic Committee, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1387)
  - Traffic Appeals Subcommittee, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1388)
  - Community College, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1389)
  - Community Concerts, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1390)
  - Computing Center-University, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1391)
  - Conferences, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1392)
  - Consulting, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1393)
  - Continuing Education Center, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1394)
  - The Counseling Center: Thomas E. Cook, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1394a)
  - Cooperative Program, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1394b)
  - Development, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 1395)
  - D-miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1396)
  - Dairy Science: Dr. J.R. Nichols, Head, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1397)
  - Dedication, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1398)
  - Pamplin Dedication #1, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1399)
  - Pamplin Dedication #2, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1400)
  - Dedication: Ambler-Johnson Hall, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1401)
  - Paul Derring Dedication, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1402)
  - Deans: General, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1403)
  - Development Council, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1404)
  - Development: Dr. Wilson B.Bell, Director, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1405)
  - Dining Hall: Mr. H.P. King, Director, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1406)
  - E-miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 37, Folder 1407)
  - Economics: Dr. W.E. Schmidt, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1408)
  - Editorial Projects for Education (EPE Report), 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1409)
  - Education: Dr. R. W. Beamer, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1410)
  - Electrical Engineering: Dr. W.A. Blackwell, Head, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1411)
  - Emeriti Letters, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1412)
  - Engineering and Buildings, Governor's Office, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1413)
  - Engineering, College of: Dean Willis G. Worcester, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1414)
  - Engineering Mechanics: Prof. D.H. Pletta, Head, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1415)
  - English: Dr. Wilson Snipes, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 1416)
  - Enrollment Statistics, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1417)
  - Entomology: Dr. J.M. Grayson, Head, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1418)
  - Equal Opportunities, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1419)
  - Esso Education Foundation, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1420)
  - Executive Bulletins, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1421)
  - Extension: General, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1422)
  - Extension Division: Dr. W.E. Skelton, Dean, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1423)
  - Extension: State Technical Services- Dr. R.L. Smith, Director #1, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1423a)
  - Extension: State Technical Service- Dr. R.L. Smith, Director #2, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1423b)
  - F-miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 36, Folder 1424)
  - Faculty Position, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1425)
  - Faculty Lists, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1426)
  - Flag Situation, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1427)
  - Faculty Promotion, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1428)
  - Ferrum Junior College, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1429)
  - First National Bank of Virginia, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1430)
  - Football, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1431)
  - Foreign Language: Dr. J. Bruhm, Head, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1432)
  - Forestry and Wildlife: Dr. J.F. Hosner, Head, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1433)
  - Foreign Service Institute, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1434)
  - Faculty Senate, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1435)
  - Forest Service Research Laboratory, 1965-1969 (Box 38, Folder 1436)
  - Final Copy: NSF Departmental Science Development Proposal, Geological Sciences, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1437)
  - G-miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1438)
  - Gallagher Presidents' Report, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1439)
  - Geological Sciences: Dr. B.N. Cooper, Head, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1440)
  - Governor's Day, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1441)
  - Glee Club: Mr. Stanley G. Kingma, Director, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1442)
  - Governor of Virginia, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1443)
  - Graduate School: Dr. F.W. Bull, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1444)
  - H-miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1445)
  - Dr. Hahn- Personal #1, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1446)
  - Dr. Hahn-Personal #2, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1447)
  - Dr. Hahn- Governorship, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1448)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1449)
  - Higher Education Facilities Act, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1450)
  - Health, Education, and Welfare, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1451)
  - History: Dr. R.G. Landen, Head, 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1452)
  - Homecoming, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 1453)
  - Home Economics, College of: Dean Laura Jane Harper, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 1454)
  - Honor Court, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 1455)
  - Horticulture: Dr. H.A. Rollins, Jr., Head, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 1456)
  - Infirmary: Dr. E.R. Irwin, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 1457)
  - Information Services: Mr. W.H. Strother, Director, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 1458)
  - I-miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 1459)